

# **ANGEL QUIÑONEZ**

**SOFTWARE DEVELOPER** 

## **ABOUT ME**

11

Computer science professional with 4+ years of experience in the IT area, specialist in the software development branch with focus on the web development, specifically at back-end although experienced in front-end technologies, using LAMP, MEAN and MEVN stacks.

Focused on reflect a work of a professional nature, minimalist, elegant and optimal performance.

Described in three words:
Conviction, Determination and Versatility.

## CONTACT

Montevideo - Uruguay Angel27y27@gmail.com +598 98 359 287

### **LANGUAGES**

Native Spanish

Conversational English

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### BACKEND/WEB DEVELOPER

Sep. 2019 - Present

Freelance

- Planning and design of the architecture and structure of an application/website, organizing the information as efficient as possible.
- Development of services (API, microservices, monolitic, according the case) that comply business expectatives.
- Creating and manage efficient databases and connect them to the solutions.
- Development of UI, ensuring that the application/website is optimally displayed in different browsers and devices.
- Guarantee connectivity and optimization of the application/website.
- Setup the security and preventing attacks.

#### **FULLSTACK DEVELOPER**

Aug. 2022 - Present

**Tata Consultancy Services** 

 Development and refactoring of modules, services, plugins and layouts of web application/websites.

#### **WEB CRAWLER**

Jun. 2022 - Aug. 2022

Remoters

Services provided for NetRivals client:

- Analyze applications/websites to find data of interest.
- Reverse engineering application.
- Development of scripts to capture data (ethically) from applications/websites.

#### WEB DEVELOPER

Sep. 2019 - Jan. 2021

Administrative Service of Identification, Migration and Immigration

- Web solutions development to make efficient common processes, replacing the existent.
- Refactor y optimize already implemented software.

## **EDUCATION**

MIDDLE TECHNICIAN IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING

2014 - 2016

Universitary College of Caracas

## **SKILLS**

MARKDOWN

HTML

SASS

CSS

VUE

ANGULAR

NODE.JS

JS

WORDPRESS

LARAVEL

PHP

MONGODB

MYSQL/MARIADB

SQL/NOSQL

**SOCIAL** 

Angsdev.github.io

@Angsdev

in @AngelQuinonezS

(Manage of the Control of the Contro